## Способы связаться

www.linkedin.com/in/dannykg (LinkedIn)

#### Основные навыки

Solution Architecture

Virtualization

Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD)

### Languages

Hebrew (Full Professional)

English (Full Professional)

Russian (Full Professional)

#### Certifications

#### **CCNA**

Google Cloud Certified Professional Cloud Architect

**A**+

**HP Networking** 

Oracle Autonomous Database Cloud Specialist

#### Honors-Awards

Colonel Outstanding Award

Amdocs - Outstanding employee of 2017

BA Degree Outstanding grade

Trailblazer Award Q1

# Danny Kaganovitch

Customer Engineer, Google Cloud @ Google Тель Авив

# Общие сведения

#helpingpeople - is my main use of LinkedIn for the past 7 years.

I connect and help people who seek jobs on a daily basis to find more opportunities, making use of my extended list of connections, I do this for free. I am not interested in creating any business opportunities around this topic.

If you are looking for a new job, please do feel free to reach out.

Myself:

10 years in the tech industry.

Roles: Instructor, Technical Support, Quality Assurance, Devops,

Technical Sales and Lead.

Industries: IT, Telco, E-Commerce and Cloud.

5 years of experience in business operations: Innovation, marketing, sales, pricing, managing, recruitment, and automation of processes.

IaaS: Google Cloud Platform, Oracle Cloud Infrastructure, Openstack, AWS.

Hypervisors: Xen, KVM, VMware.

Services: Compute, Network, Storage, Security, IaaC, Devops, CI/

CD, Docker, Kubernetes, Serverless.

Network Engineering and Telco:

I have deep knowledge of Networking

(studied for CCIE R&S).

In planning, executing configuring and troubleshooting network topologies.

Deep TCP/IP knowledge - network protocols, Routing and Switching & Load Balancers.

Worked with different vendors, both physical appliances and virtual network functions.

Cloud networking - Juniper Contrail, and Orchestrator.

## Operating Systems:

I am very comfortable with different distributions of Linux.

Personal preference - Mac.

No problem with Windows - but I do prefer others..

#### Code & Automation skills:

I Write Automation scripts in Python, Bash, Ansible, Terraform, Power shell, and more.

#### CI/CD & SCM:

Github, Bitbucket, Gitlab, Jenkins, Hudson, Helm Charts, ArgoCD, Flux, Linkerd, Pipelines, Service mesh, Gitops and Progressive Deployments.

## Entrepreneurship:

I had founded Prodicty.

I had launched multiple internet products from 0 to growing income/ exit.

#### E-commerce:

I've been selling for more than 5 years online, on Amazon, Shopify and Woo Commerce.

#### Personal skills:

I volunteer as an instructor and I have been teaching for years,

I learn and adapt quickly.

I have great communication skills,

I have strong business orientation.

I believe I'm a good team player and mentor,

and i'm open for improving myself and others.

#### My biggest achievements so far:

- \* Helped hundreds of people in finding jobs through Linkedin and connections.
- \* Sold a private label brand that I created from 0.
- \* Reached 25km running

# Опыт работы

# Google

Customer Engineer Google Cloud Platform октября 2021 - Present (8 месяцев)

Tel Aviv, Israel

Infrastructure Modernization

**Prodicty** 

Co-Founder, COO ноября 2019 - Present (2 года 7 месяцев)

Israel

Prodicty is a software that makes money for online sellers, by scanning bulk spreadsheets of products, suggesting which products to buy and sell on Amazon.

We created 75% monthly ROI from products we found in our research process while using Prodicty, we created a portfolio of 100 unique products to our Amazon store.

Prodicty brings a new approach when it comes to market research, sales tracking and new opportunities for Amazon sellers.

Prodicty saves time and money, using automated product research process. 1 hour of running a scan = 3 months of manual human research.

Prodicty eliminates bad decisions, and suggests accurate deals which are based on data like: ROI, demand, competition, risks, restrictions and 200 different factors.

I had the opportunity to managed a team of 5 software developers, 2 researchers and 2 purchasing specialist, who I recruited for this project.

Oracle

1 год 6 месяцев

Principal Cloud Solution Architect июня 2021 - сентября 2021 (4 месяца)

Israel

As a Principal Sales Consultant, I was helping Oracle customers/partners with migrating and running their workloads in Oracle Cloud Infrastructure.

- \* I was working closely with sales and product in order to bring customers the maximum value, based on feedbacks and business requirements.
- \* I was consulting and assisting with any technical and business case that is raised and involves tech or cloud solutions.
- \* I was presenting at conferences to technical and C level stakeholders, with Oracle's offerings in IaaS and PaaS.
- \* I was hosting internal and external technical webinars, workshops and participating in joint venture tech talks.
- \* I was part of Oracle's EMEA Cloud Native CoP, which I was responsible in promoting our Cloud Native products, knowledge and positioning.
- \* I was helping customers with adoption of Cloud Native, Open Source and Cloud solutions such as IaaC, Kubernetes, Functions and many more..
- \* I was helping in educating with proper Devops methodologies and development efficiency (CI/CD, Pipelines and anything that can help organizations to improve their software release and make the development process easier.
- \* I was part of Oracle Israel volunteering leaders, I participated in planning and executing community volunteering.

Senior Cloud Solution Architect апреля 2020 - июня 2021 (1 год 3 месяца) Petah Tiqwa, Central, Israel

#### Amdocs

4 года 9 месяцев

DevOps Specialist августа 2018 - апреля 2020 (1 год 9 месяцев)

- Managed a remote deployment team for large Telco customers.
- I was responsible for our lab maintenance and installations, which had more than 500 servers.

- I installed and managed Openstack as our private cloud which was allocated for more than 200 R&D team members.
- I built docker images in GO, which was part of our automation toolset.
- I automated deployments by writing Terraform, Ansible, Bash and Python scripts.
- I was responsible for our self managed Kubernetes clusters.
- I contributed and maintained our CI/CD Pipelines, in Jenkins and Gitlab, which had more than 1,000 different build jobs.
- I installed different tools such as SDN Controllers, Monitoring systems and automation frameworks.
- I worked on large and complex customer deployment projects.
- I enjoyed integrating different Open Source technologies.
- I participated in bringing new technological solutions to our Dev teams.
- I promoted FinOps approach as part of my resource awareness.

Automation Engineer августа 2015 - августа 2018 (3 года 1 месяц) Israel

Projects: NCSO, ASDC, D2 - AT&T, Comcast, Vodafone. Services: SD-WAN, VPN site-to-site, VSRX, Virtual FWs...

I installed and tested SDN & NFV integrative platforms.

I worked on different features such as: Monitoring - Healing & Scaling , ElasticSearch, UI, net-conf adaptor, plugins, Collectd.

I worked with VNFs from different vendors- Versa, Juniper VSRX, Fortinet and etc..

I worked with Openstack projects: Neutron, Glance, Cinder, Ceilometer, Contrail.

I worked with network Cloud Orchestrator,

Tested Site to Site L2&L3VPN Connection.

Worked with different Linux distributions - RHEL, Centos and Ubuntu.

I used different Databases - RIAK, Postgres, MySQL, and Oracle.

I performed security tests via Nessus.

I wrote automation tests in Python (Pycharm & pyTest).

I wrote automation tests in frameworks such as Jmeter & Jenkins.

I tested Python Rest API Framework.

Day to day tools:

Code Management: Git, Gerrit - code review.

Code: Python, Javascript, Selenium for UI Testing.

Service Design: Designing in SDC & MEC.

Bynet Data Communications Technical Support Engineer сентября 2014 - августа 2015 (1 год)

Israel

I installed new network environments for medium/large organizations including data center and routing.

I troubleshooted & solved latency and configuration problems in different networks and vendors.

I built projects, writing LLD's and ATP's.

My network vendors experience is: Cisco - Nexus/Catalyst/Routers, HP/3COM - Procurve/Comware, Juniper -EX/M/MX Series, Avaya/Nortel, Dell, RAD and

etc...

Field experience: Building small/medium size multi vendor networks,

Enterprise switching and routing, backbone core technologies and data center switching.

configuring APs ,troubleshooting and analyzing L2/L3 networks.

Network management, monitoring and security: HP IMC, Snmpc, Spectrum, PRTG, Solarwinds, Checkpoint appliance, NAC - Portnox, Wireshark (For analyze).

I have deep knowledge of the following protocols and technologies: TCP/IP, Ethernet, MPLS, VRF, Vlans, STP, RSTP, PVST, MST, VTP, GRE, QOS, NAT, ACL, Policy routing, IP SLA/NQA, BFD, TCP/UDP, RIP, EIGRP, OSPF, BGP, PPP, PPoE, Cisco CEF, VPN-Client, IPSeC, Port-channel/LAG, FHRP, Stack, IRF, VPC, AAA, SNMP, Syslog, NTP.

Israel Defense Forces
Network & System Instructor
августа 2011 - августа 2014 (3 года 1 месяц)
I commanded and instructed soldiers at IDF.

I though TCP/IP fundamentals, CCNA preparation course, basic computer systems and some military technologies.

I designed and configuring network topologies, with network equipment from different vendors such as Cisco and Juniper.

I installed and configured Windows Exchange , Active Directory Servers, and Polycom equipment for VC.

I was responsible for groups of 20+ soldiers for almost 2.5 years.

I was a tech lead for a team of 2-3 commanders.

I though other group of commanders and instructors with new technologies.

I pushed new innovations.

# Образование

Ruppin Academic Center

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), Business Administration and

Management, General · (2016 - 2019)

Neve Haddasah

High School Diploma, Network and System Administration/ Administrator · (2004 - 2011)